Aaron K Greenyer

Mobile: +44 7498 731 198 Email: akgreenyer@gmail.com Website: akgre.github.io

A **solution focused** test automation engineer incorporating applied knowledge of electronic test equipment with **software frameworks** and **data analytics** to accelerate your testing capabilities.

Combine your expertise with **real visualisation** of product performance to confidently achieve your engineering and business goals. Practising open and transparent collaboration to implement requirements for the optimum solution from the point of view of **functionality** and **cost effectiveness**.

Focus Areas

Design & Support

Supporting you to define dynamic improvement of your test strategies for increasingly complex R&D requirements

Process Workflow

Software Development

Pragmatic development of a scalable modular design offers tailored support for your project development

Learn More:

Test Automation Framework

Data Analytics

See the value of your data throughout the product lifecycle by providing greater insight for effective decision making

Data Visualization

Employment

<u>Contracting Engineer</u> – Greenyer Electronics LTD

Developing automated test applications for customer products

3/2017 - Current

- Working with experts to accelerate progress and accomplish their project goals
- Develop a bespoke python framework to rapidly design and execute product test procedures

Learn More: Contract Experience

<u>Technical Support Engineer</u> – Keysight Technologies (AKA Agilent/HP) 6/2014 – 3/2017 Supporting customers selecting new instruments, application methods and fault diagnosis

- Trained in multiple disciplines to support customers on a wide range of test and measurement applications
- Liaising with multiple technical teams locally and around the world to form solutions to customer's inquiries
- Introducing software integration support to an industry that is evolving



- Develop applications to organise query threads and store backups for reference and training
- Managing and assisting with training of new staff

<u>Laboratory Manager</u> – Pure (Wireless Music Systems Company) 12/2010 – 6/2014 Running an electronic laboratory, assisting design engineers and designing product test solutions

- Designing and developing RF test automation solutions
- Product system verification testing
- Hardware development, board modifications
- Lab management organising and maintaining lab, maintaining lab equipment, computers and procurement of stock
- PCB design and manufacture

Robotics Process Automation

In some instances, recreating the functions of repetitive manual tasks for automation is not justifiable. The applications that are already in use can be complex and the amount of resource required would not see a return on investment.

On these occasions I have used Robotic Process Automation (RPA) to develop rule-based processes that mimic the steps a human would take to perform the process. The software uses the existing user interface and can be integrated into the test execution in a short time; which means that RPA can quickly create value.

Computing And Technical Skills

- Experienced knowledge of Windows OS, Windows Office
- Data analysis with product testing
- Applied knowledge of Python to design and develop automated tests for product testing
- Object Oriented Programming (OOP) design
- Use of GIT version control system
- Accomplished SMD soldering skills and techniques with re-flow soldering
- Product thermal testing in climatic chambers
- RF testing in anechoic chambers
- Computer hardware (build and setup computers with dual boot Ubuntu/Windows)
- Use of data visualization tools (Tableau)

- Proficient knowledge of test and measurement equipment. DMMs, oscilloscopes, generators, analysers etc.
- Use of Prologix ethernet to GPIB adapters
- Working knowledge of VBA, VEE, LabVIEW
- Communication with DUT via SPI, I2C, RS232, JTAG, Ethernet and USB.
- Hardware Prototyping
- Parts stock and assent management
- Good working knowledge of Raspberry Pi and Arduino (use of C/C++)
- Experience with fault finding and bug reporting
- Understanding of electronic schematics

Education

Electronic and Electrical Engineering Foundation	Brunel University, Uxbridge		09/2007 - 05/2008	
Engineering Mathematics Devices & Circuits Computers & Digital Systems	B A B	Personal & Analytical Workshop Business managemen		B A A
	Richmond College, Twickenham		09/2004 - 06/2007	
A-levels: A/S levels:	Electronics, Physics, Chemistry and Mathematics Music Technology			
	Elthorne Park High School, Hanwell		09/1999 - 07/2004	
11 GCSEs including:	English, Maths, Physics, Chemistry and Biology.			
	Investing 8	2,		

Investing & Outsourcing

As projects evolve, it may be necessary to expand the testing capabilities and invest or upgrade test systems. With inside knowledge of test and measurement manufacturers, I am able to coordinate with third party suppliers to provide technical support, prove equipment performance and present financial options for your solution.

I have worked closely with a **Data Scientist** who specialises in creating statistical programs which display optimized statistical efficiency and quality amongst thousands of tests. Further, I use these elegant visualizations for communicating insights to decision makers as well as storing and demonstrating the output across the history of a product's development.